Alessio Palumbo

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a passionate Junior Web Developer who joined the community attracted by the opportunity to solve people's real problems at a global scale. I am a dedicated member of the team who loves to learn new skills, works hard to get things done and gets along with everybody.

EXPERIENCE

Coder Academy, Melbourne, Vic — Bootcamper

August 2017 - March 2018

Html5, Css3, Javascript, Ruby, Rails, MEAN stack, React, Git

Kodama Coffee, Williamstown, Vic — Head Chef

October 2016- July 2017

The Builders Arms Hotel, Fitzroy, Vic — Commis Chef

February 2016 - October 2016

Three One 2 One, Richmond, Vic — Chef de Partie

October 2014 - January 2016

Park Hyatt Hotel, Melbourne, Vic — Commis Chef

January 2014 - March 2015

Coffea, Melbourne, Vic — Chef Assistant

May 2013 - May 2014

Pie Face Pty ltd, Melbourne, Vic — Team Leader

May 2012 - April 2013

CPO&Partners Co., Ltd., Shanghai — Assistant Manager

June 2010 - July 2011

Liaised with local suppliers and consultants, Processed orders, Market research, Prepared and Attended meetings, Answered calls and emails. Performed Interpreting and Translation, Quality control, Bookkeeping.

EDUCATION

Ca' Foscari, Venice — Ba in Culture & Language Mediation

September 2006 - March 2010

Mandarin Chinese, English, Interpreting and Translation.

LINKS

alessio-palumbo.netlify.com github.com/alessio-palumbo linkedin.com/in/alessio-palumbo twitter.com/_alessiopalumbo

PROJECTS

Instarails

https://github.com/alessio-palumbo/instarails

ChefBasket

https://github.com/alessio-palumbo/ChefBasket

MyPortfolio

https://github.com/alessio-palu

mbo/my-portfolio

RailsBnb

https://github.com/alessio-palumbo/rails_bnb

WEB DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

HTML5

CSS₃

Javascript(Es6)

Ruby

Rails

Node.js

React.js

Git

Figma

PERSONAL SKILLS

Management

Leadership

Organization

Teamwork

Customer Service

Creativity

LANGUAGES

Italian: Native
English: Fluent
Mandarin: Fluent